<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Kadin Codes</title>
    <link href="https://kadin.codes/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://kadin.codes" />
    <updated>2026-01-19T15:55:50-06:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Kadin Van Valin</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://kadin.codes</id>

    <entry>
        <title>show your work</title>
        <author>
            <name>Kadin Van Valin</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://kadin.codes/show-your-work.html"/>
        <id>https://kadin.codes/show-your-work.html</id>

        <updated>2024-02-21T15:43:00-06:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I take a lot of notes. No. More than that. There are messy and I don't have a goal for any of it. I fill&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p><br>I take a lot of notes. No. More than that. There are messy and I don't have a goal for any of it. I fill my todo app with ideas, names of new people I meet and projects that I think would be fun to execute on. I write in notebooks, on printer paper and eventually a lot ends up in a giant markdown document. The notes are incomplete and often I lose enough context that they have no value after a week or two.<br><br>In L.A. last week I was introduced to a new book. Show your work by Austin Kleon. I have often come across the idea that it is essential to have an online presence, and a blog is needed to grow a software career, but that isn't something that I find very compelling.<br>I hate talking about myself, and if I wanted to go into sales I would have. No, I may try in fits and starts, but marketing yourself for the purpose of marketing yourself doesn't resonate with me. Show your work makes a slightly different argument. As a follow-up to Steal like an artist, Austin argues that having an online presence is about allowing others to steal from you. <br><br>Furthermore, I like the idea of creating a space to steal from myself. Instead of the rushed scribbling that can lead to forgetting the original intent, something published should (hopefully) have a little more context, be more formal and make more sense in a year from now when I am reviewing what I have worked on.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>League of Legends &quot;creep&quot; score</title>
        <author>
            <name>Kadin Van Valin</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://kadin.codes/league-of-legends-creep-score.html"/>
        <id>https://kadin.codes/league-of-legends-creep-score.html</id>

        <updated>2021-08-08T15:40:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    League of Legends is an online tower defense game. A core compenent of the game is landing the killing blow on minions that defend the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>League of Legends is an online tower defense game. A core compenent of the game is landing the killing blow on minions that defend the towers. The count of this is normally called creep score, or cs.<br>In 2006 I signed up for a skills course by thinkful (now out of business) to learn html, javascript and css. The capstone project was to create a site that integrated with an API. The site is broken now because league of legends api has changed. I added a demo button to make it easier to see how the site functioned in 2006.</p>
<p> </p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://kadin.codes/media/posts/4/lol-creep-score.png" alt="poorly made dashboard]" width="3342" height="1846" sizes="(min-width: 920px) 703px, (min-width: 700px) calc(82vw - 35px), calc(100vw - 81px)" srcset="https://kadin.codes/media/posts/4/responsive/lol-creep-score-xs.png 300w ,https://kadin.codes/media/posts/4/responsive/lol-creep-score-sm.png 480w ,https://kadin.codes/media/posts/4/responsive/lol-creep-score-md.png 768w ,https://kadin.codes/media/posts/4/responsive/lol-creep-score-lg.png 1024w"></figure>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Enders Quiz</title>
        <author>
            <name>Kadin Van Valin</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://kadin.codes/enders-quiz.html"/>
        <id>https://kadin.codes/enders-quiz.html</id>

        <updated>2021-08-07T15:38:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Enders game is a 1985 Sciencefiction novel written by Orson Scott card. In 2007 I had just finished a skills course by thinkful. I was&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Enders game is a 1985 Science<span style="font-size: inherit;">fiction novel written by Orson Scott card. </span></p>
<p>In 2007 I had just finished a skills course by thinkful. I was starting to look for employment and was<span style="font-size: inherit;"> unsure if I had the skills needed to be marketable. </span></p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  style="font-size: inherit;" src="https://kadin.codes/media/posts/3/enders-quiz.png" alt="Image of a poorly made quiz" width="3560" height="1904" sizes="(min-width: 920px) 703px, (min-width: 700px) calc(82vw - 35px), calc(100vw - 81px)" srcset="https://kadin.codes/media/posts/3/responsive/enders-quiz-xs.png 300w ,https://kadin.codes/media/posts/3/responsive/enders-quiz-sm.png 480w ,https://kadin.codes/media/posts/3/responsive/enders-quiz-md.png 768w ,https://kadin.codes/media/posts/3/responsive/enders-quiz-lg.png 1024w"></figure><br>It took me another year, and a stint at chicagos dev boot camp until I landed my first job.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
